<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Visual Analog Scale</string>
    <string name="KEY_PREFERENCES_GENERATOR_MESSAGE" translatable="false">generator_message</string>
    <string name="KEY_PREFERENCES_RATINGS" translatable="false">ratings</string>
    <string name="KEY_PREFERENCES_SEED" translatable="false">seed</string>
    <string name="KEY_PREFERENCES_SESSION_ID" translatable="false">session_id</string>
    <string name="DIRECTORY_NAME_RESULTS" translatable="false">Results</string>
    <string name="action_quit">Quit</string>
    <string name="action_reset_ratings">Create a new session</string>
    <string name="action_help">Help</string>
    <string name="action_show_session_info">Session Info</string>
    <string name="alert">Alert</string>
    <string name="button_pause_label">Pause</string>
    <string name="button_play_label">Play</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="checkmark">Checkmark</string>
    <string name="close_confirm_prompt">Are you sure you want to quit\?</string>
    <string name="main_title">Intelligibility</string>
    <string name="next_track">Next</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="previous_track">Previous</string>
    <string name="rating_label_highest">Perfectly Intelligible</string>
    <string name="rating_label_lowest">Completely unintelligible</string>
    <string name="reset_confirm_prompt">Are you sure you want to reset all current ratings and start a new rating session\\?</string>
    <string name="session_info_title">Info</string>
    <string name="toast_connect_headphones">Please, plug in headphones.</string>
    <string name="toast_increase_volume">Audio volume is muted.</string>
    <string name="track">Recording</string>
    <string name="welcome_title">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="welcome_message">
        Welcome to speech recordings rating using visual analog scales application.\n\n
        This application was developed for use in research and development in the department of circuit theory, faculty of electrotechnics, CTU in Prague.\n\n
        You can begin the rating process by listening to the first audio recording, after you confirm this window.\n\n
        You can display the application toolbar by swiping down from the top of the screen.
    </string>
    <string name="session_info_message">
        Session information (debug purpose only):\n\n
        Session ID: %s\n\n
        Generated: %s\n\n
        Seed: %s\n\n
        Rated: %s\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="RATING_FILE_NAME" translatable="false">
        RATING_%d_%s.txt
    </string>
    <string name="track_time_placeholder" translatable="false">00:00</string>
    <string name="track_counter" translatable="false">%s: %d/%d</string>
    <string name="directory_selection_instructions">
        Audio file placement instructions:\n
        Place your audio speech recordings saved as WAV or MP3-files in an accessible directory
        (e.g. <i>Documents</i>) on internal memory or SD-card.\n\n
        There have to be following folders in the selected directory:\n
        <tt>\"HC\"</tt>, <tt>\"DBS_OFF\"</tt> and <tt>\"DBS_130\"</tt>\n
        With audio files belonging to the groups placed within, accordingly.\n\n
        This app <i>currently</i> only supports this predefined system, and will be
        upgraded to auto-recognize group names in the future versions.
    </string>
    <string name="not_implemented">This function is not yet implemented.</string>
    <string name="KEY_PREFERENCES_STATE" translatable="false">state</string>
    <string name="all_rated">All recordings have been rated!</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="help_message">
        This app is used for easy subjective scoring of speech recording intelligibility by listeners.
        Precise use of the application depends on the experiment being conducted, but the general
        aim of the application was to subjectively rate speech deterioration in patients suffering
        from neurodegenerative diseases.\n\n
        Assuming you have correctly placed the speech recording files into the specified folder on the
        phone\'s SD card (as is described in the dialog shown in case the application was not able
        to find any data), using the app is fairly simple.\n\n
        The application automatically randomizes the loaded recordings during the creation of a new
        rating session (resetting the current session). The recordings are then played using the
        provided application interface. Listener uses the \"play\" and \"pause\" buttons and the seek bar
        to listen to the recordings, changing between them using the \"next\" and \"previous\" buttons.
        Total recording count as well as the number of the current recording is displayed in the
        header.\n\n
        Recordings are rated using the Visual Analog Scale in the lower part of the screen. User simply
        places the seek button on the desired position on the track, which represents the subjectively
        perceived speech intelligibility of the speaker\'s voice, in range from \"completely
        unintelligible\" (no words comprehended) to \"perfectly intelligible\" (TV reporter level).
        The number of ratings and backward editing of the ratings are not restricted, nevertheless
        users should be instructed to listen to the recordings twice in maximum. After a recording
        is successfully rated, a green checkmark sign will appear.\n\n
        A double green checkmark sign will show up after all the provided recordings have been rated,
        along with a brief message. The ratings will be automatically saved to the application folder
        on the phone\'s memory card while the application is closed. The rating progress in the scope
        of one rating session is also automatically preserved in the case of closing or exiting the app,
        right until a new session is requested by the user, or up to the occasion of a reinstall.\n\n
        If you encounter any problems using the app, please send a mail to:\n
        kryzepet@fel.cvut.cz
    </string>
    <string name="choose_data_dir">Choose the data directory</string>
    <string name="KEY_PREFERENCES_DATADIR" translatable="false">datadir</string>
    <string name="KEY_PREFERENCES_FILELIST" translatable="false">filelist</string>
    <string name="no_session_found">No previous rating session was found. Please create a new session.</string>
    <string name="corrupted_session">Previous session is corrupted. Please create a new session.</string>
    <string name="info">Info</string>
    <string name="create_new_session">Create new session</string>
    <string name="directory_not_exist">Directory <i>%1$s</i> does not exist.</string>
    <string name="directory_not_directory">Selection <i>%1$s</i> is not a directory.</string>
    <string name="directory_not_readable">Directory <i>%1$s</i> is not readable.</string>
    <string name="directory_no_files">No usable audio files were found in the <i>%1$s</i> directory.</string>
    <string name="directory_missing_files">The loaded session is missing the following files (total %1$d) in the directory %2$s:\n%3$s</string>
    <string name="choose_valid_data_dir">Choose valid data directory</string>
    <string name="internal_error_URI_extract_failed">Internal error!\nError message: Extracting full path from document selection URI failed!</string>
    <string name="error">Error</string>
    <string name="action_save">Save</string>
    <string name="save_success">Saving successful!</string>
    <string name="save_failed">Saving failed!\nReason: %1$s</string>
    <string name="save_failed_continue_question">Saving failed!\nReason: %1$s \nDo you want to continue with creating a new session? Current ratings will be lost.</string>
    <string name="save_failed_continue_title">Warning</string>
</resources>